(Penny:)Well, since Amy's going, do you want me
there, you know, to support you?
Oh. That's nice, but it's just gonna be
a room full of boring old men.
(Leonard:)I'm not sure how much help you'd be.
(Penny:)Okay. I'm just gonna tie my shoe
while you think about that. Ahem.
(Leonard:)Oh, yeah. No, thanks.
That would be great help.
(Leonard:)- You realize you might kill some of them.
- Then you all can get tenure.
(Raj:)Come on, Daddy.
All the other scientists have seat warmers.
(Raj:)This is so humiliating.
I've got to get tenure.
(Raj:)Okay, let's meet halfway. How about I
cut my cleaning lady down to twice a week?
(Raj:)Looks like we're both going to be
living like animals.
(Amy:)Let's go over our emotional responses
one last time.
(Sheldon:)Okay.